(SINGING) It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
- Mom, are we there yet?
- Almost, Chris.
Now remember, kids,
when we get to Mr. Quagmire's cabin,
don't touch anything
before I have a chance to disinfect it.
Boy, it was nice of Quagmire
to let us use his place.
This'll be much better
than that vacation we took
with The Price is Right yodeler.
(YODELING)
Okay, you can stop here.
There's no way that microwave costs
more than 300 bucks. Stop here!
Don't... Don't listen to that fat tourist.
She doesn't know
how much a microwave costs. Stop!
(LOSER THEME FROM
THE PRICE IS RIGHT PLA YS)
(SIGHS) We should've gone to Plinko
like Cleveland.
(LAUGHING)
(GROANS)
Oh, Dad,
I think this is Mr. Quagmire's driveway.
Didn't he say it was between
two big oak trees?
Well, there's a lot of trees around here.
How do we know we're in the right spot?
PETER: I think it's a safe bet
this is the place.
Well, this looks comfortable.
(SIGHS) This is gonna be
a relaxing weekend.
(DISCO MUSIC PLA YING)
(THUDDING)
- Hey, did you hear something?
- I think it came from upstairs.
(EX CLAIMING)
Oh. Hey. This is the week
you guys were coming up?
Huh.
And here I am, cream on my face,
hair a mess, and in mid-coitus.
I must look a sight.
- Beautiful country, isn't it, Chris?
- God, it is peaceful. No question, Dad.
Just be careful, 'cause they got
a lot of big old wilderness bugs out here.
Oh, hey, y'all best be careful
or I'm gonna sting you with my stinger.
Oh, no!
But then I's gonna die if I sting you.
You know what?
I'm not gonna sting y'all after all.
And that's my choice. Y'all ain't worth it.
I'm just gonna head on over to that flower
and suck on that stamen
like there's no tomorrow.
Brian, how many years have I been saying
you and I should go berry picking?
- A lot of years, Stewie.
- Wait a minute.
Do you know where we are, Brian?
This is a very special place.
They say once every 100 years in this spot,
Donny Most rises from the mist.
- I think that's just a legend.
- Well, that's because you're...
(GASPS) Look!
(SINGING) Donny Most
Donny Most
He was Ralph on Happy Days
Now he rises
From the haze
Actually, it's Don Most now.
Donny Most
Sunday, Monday
Happy Days
Now, watch carefully, you guys.
Out here in the woods,
you got to hang your food up high
so the Pope won't get it.
You gotta da hot links?
Come on, the Pope-a want-a da hot links.
(GRUNTS)
All right, who's ready
for a campfire song, huh?
- Oh, come on, Dad, that's lame.
- It's not lame, Meg.
Look, those people over there
are having a good time.
(SINGING) She'll be coming
round the mountain
When she comes
She'll be coming round the mountain
All right, here's a little tune
inspired by one of the great legends
of the Old West.
(SINGING) Well, there once
were two cowboys
All alone out on the trail
And they discovered they could sleep
With another male
Now they're having butt sex
Cowboy butt sex
Sodomy
Come on, everybody.
Sodomy.
And when he woke up in the morning,
she was still in his bed!
(SCREAMS)
- That's it?
- Yeah.
And then she wanted to make him eggs!
(SCREAMS)
And he said, " Oh, I don't have time,
I've got a meeting at 12:30."
And she said, "I'll drive you there!"
(SCREAMS)
And he said, " No, no, it's at my office.
It's like a half-hour commute."
And she said, " I don't mind,
it's on the way to my kid's pre-school."
(SCREAMING)
Hey, Lois, look at me,
I got post-partum depression!
(MOCK CRYING)
I'm sad about stuff!
(GASPS) You son of a bitch!
Don't even joke about that!
- This water feels kind of funny.
- Yeah, and it smells bad.
(EX CLAIMS)
- Dad, look!
- Holy crap!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Oh, my God,
what the hell is wrong with this lake?
I think it's a safe bet that
that's responsible.
So they can just dump their waste
into the lake? This can't be legal.
What kind of world is this
where you can't even trust
the oil companies anymore?
- Hey, you've got a tattoo.
- No, I don't.
- Is that Ziggy?
- No.
- You have a Ziggy tattoo?
- Jesus.
- Why do you have a Ziggy tattoo?
- I just used to think he was kind of funny.
We should...
We should get to the hospital.
Mom, how long do we have to
wear these wigs?
Until our hair grows back, Chris.
Dad, you couldn't have gotten us anything
more stylish?
Oh, I don't think it's so bad.
I feel rather like Mozart.
Hey, Stewie, play Haydn.
Now play Handel.
- Play Peter Griffin.
- Now that is a challenge.
(FARTING)
Go ahead, mock me.
But it wasn't Stewie
who was laughing at me. It was God!
(DRAMA TIC MUSIC PLA YING)
What can I do for you, Mrs. Griffin?
Mayor West,
I'm here as an outraged citizen.
The Quahog Oil Refinery is emptying
all their toxic waste into the lake.
I mean, you couldn't possibly
have sanctioned
that kind of blatant industrial pollution,
could you?
- Yeah, I told them it was fine.
- What?
And in return, I get free oil for my hair.
Hey, baby, want some Adam West penis?
This is unbelievable!
Well, I am not gonna stand by
while you let this town be destroyed
by corruption!
Mr. Mayor, I promise you this.
Next election, I'm gonna run against you,
and I'm gonna win.
All right, Mrs. Griffin,
you wanna take me on, fine.
But if you plan to beat me, you'll have to...
(GASPS)
- What is it?
- A bee just flew in through the window.
Don't move.
Hmm. Now look who's mayor.
First order of business,
free honey for everyone!
Yay! Mayor Bee! Mayor Bee! Mayor Bee!
(EX CLAIMS IN PAIN)
Done stung myself. Bye, world.
- Good evening, Quahog. I'm Tom Tucker.
- And I'm Diane Simmons.
The Quahog mayoral race is heating up
with incumbent Adam West squaring off
against challenger Lois Griffin.
Which leads many political analysts
to ask the question,
can a woman really be mayor?
Or will she just bleed all over the city?
Stay with us.
Oh, you guys, I can't tell you
how much I appreciate all your hard work.
It's really gonna make a difference
with my campaign.
Hey, Lois, take a look.
I just made 500 T-shirts
that say,
"Vote for Lois, unless you're queer."
"No, wait, even if you're queer.
No Jews, though. Okay, Jews."
Oh, these are wonderful, sweetie.
Chris, why don't you put these upstairs
in your closet so we don't lose them?
But the evil monkey lives in my closet.
Of course, he hasn't been as evil
since he became a Jehovah's Witness.
(RINGS DOORBELL)
(DOOR OPENING)
Hi, I'm going door-to-door to campaign
on behalf of Lois Griffin,
who's offering real change
for the city of Quahog.
- May we count on your vote next Tuesday?
- Chris, this is our house.
Ah.
Then what is for dinner?
- Pork chops.
- Excellent.
Chris, have you been to any other houses?
I have not.
- Would you like to come in?
- Please.
This is Tom Tucker
with some breaking election coverage.
Mayor Adam West has widened his lead
over challenger Lois Griffin.
I'm confident that the people of Quahog
will make the right choice.
And here to help me secure
the Latino vote
is actor Jimmy Smits.
Adam West likes to eat food
that's grilled in foil.
(ALL CHATTERING EX CITEDLY)
That's our guy!
Boy, this election's gonna be a tight one.
It's probably gonna be decided
by just a couple of votes.
And here we are sitting here
like a bunch of lazy paraplegic cops.
- Huh?
- I'm sorry, Joe, it's just an expression.
Ah.
We got to give Lois a last-minute edge.
Guys, I need you to help out
on the campaign.
Oh, man. That's like making all, like, signs
and walking around or what?
You know,
you bastards got a stake in this, too.
I mean, Lois is my wife,
and if she's the mayor,
we can pretty much do
whatever the hell we want.
I could do cocaine if I wanted to.
- Peter, you want some potatoes?
- Yeah, how you doing?
- I was just asking if you wanted...
- We got enough napkins?
Yeah, we got enough napkins.
That's enough. That's enough, right there.
(SIGHS)
What time is it?
Is that... Is that straight?
Is that straight right there?
Wait, wait, wait. See, I'll fix it. No, no.
Is that straight? I can't...
(SHOUTING)
Meg, sweep that up. Just get a broom.
Sweep that up.
Sweep that up. Put it up in your room,
but sweep it up first!
Suspect number two,
he's the one who raped me.
All right.
All but number two are free to leave.
Ma'am, I know that you're going through
a difficult time right now,
but I just have a few more questions.
Are you planning to vote tomorrow?
- What?
- Are you aware that Lois Griffin has a plan
to cut property tax in half
over the next three years?
What does that have to do
with what happened to me?
Well, you say number two did it,
maybe I say I smell alcohol on your breath.
You can't do that!
Sounds like Lois Griffin
can count on your vote.
Hi, when you go to vote
for Mayor tomorrow,
please vote for Lois Griffin.
That's right. I work at a deli,
and I know baloney.
And that's exactly what you'll get
with Mayor Adam West.
(CHUCKLING) Oh, snap.
Boy, you guys, I really appreciate
all the help you've been giving us.
Except for you, Quagmire,
you ain't done nothing.
What the hell you talking about?
Lois is gonna get the entire female vote
'cause of me.
I've been having sex
with every woman in town nonstop
for the past two days.
My God, if I tried to masturbate right now,
you know what'd come out?
A little flag with the word "bang" on it.
(LAUGHS)
Welcome, Quahog,
to the town hall mayoral debate
between incumbent Adam West
and challenger Lois Griffin.
We will now open up the floor
to questions from a community at large.
Yes, Mrs. Griffin, how do you feel
about those computer websites
that put a blue square on the home
of a sex offender?
Well, the safety of our children
is a very important part of my plan
for Quahog.
I have a 12-point program
for the security...
I'm sorry, your time is up.
(ALL MURMURING)
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no. I'm not impressed.
I'm not impressed. Not yet.
Mayor West, if re-elected,
would you increase the frequency
of garbage pick up?
Well, citizen, that's an excellent question
and I thank you for it.
I think it's great we live in a town
where you can ask questions,
because without questions,
we'd just have answers.
And an answer without a question
is a statement.
Oh, I like him! He looks me in the eye!
(ALL CHATTERING EX CITEDLY)
I'd like to have a beer with him.
I'm voting for him.
I don't understand these people.
He didn't even say anything
and they're eating it up.
Lois, undecided voters
are the biggest idiots on the planet.
Try giving short, simple answers.
Sir, your question, please.
Mrs. Griffin, what do you plan to do
about crime in our city?
A lot.
(ALL CHATTERING EX CITEDLY)
Because that's what Jesus wants.
9/11 was bad.
(ALL CHEERING)
- I agree with that!
- God, I can't believe how easy this is.
Mrs. Griffin, what are your plans
for cleaning up our environment?
9/11.
(ALL CHEERING)
Mrs. Griffin,
what about our traffic problem?
- 9...
- ALL: Huh?
...11.
(ALL CHEERING)
Well, the election results are pouring in
and it looks like it's gonna be a tight one.
Which reminds me, Diane,
when's the last time you heard... Forget it.
Oh, my God, I'm an absolute wreck.
Well, folks, this is it.
The last of the votes have been tallied,
and we're getting the final results in now.
Quahog's new mayor is...
Lois Griffin!
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, oh, God!
Oh. Were we done cheering?
(LAUGHS)
- Well, Mrs. Mayor, how do you feel?
- Oh, I'm a little nervous, Brian,
but mostly I'm excited
about all the good I'm gonna get to do.
Wow, look at you. All that power
and you've still got that body.
And the first thing I'm gonna do as mayor
is clean up Lake Quahog.
Well, I know the people
will support you, Lois,
because you connect with them,
like Disney connects with its audience.
- You the cow!
- No, you the cow!
Wow, Disney gets us!
And I think we all realize
the importance of stopping
the environmental damage
being done to Lake Quahog.
Which is why I'm proposing
a very modest tax increase
that will help us to...
(ALL BOOING)
No, no, no. That's awful.
No, no, no. I'm not okay with that.
- No new taxes.
- ALL: No new taxes!
No new taxes! No new taxes!
But what about the terrorists?
(ALL GASP)
That's right. Terrorists.
We have intelligence that suggests
that Hitler is plotting with...
With the Legion of Doom
to assassinate Jesus.
Using the lake as a base.
(ALL MURMURING)
ANNOUNCER: Meanwhile,
at the Legion of Doom...
How did she discover our plan?
Me, Solomon Grundy,
kind of dropped the ball on that one.
And we also have evidence
that Darth Vader tried
to buy yellowcake uranium
from unwed teenage mothers.
Those things all sound scary!
How much money
before I can feel safe again?
(STAMMERS)
A hundred thousand?
(ALL MURMURING)
I threw a 10!
See that 10 there? I threw that.
At the top of the news,
Lake Quahog is once again clean
thanks to the efforts
of newly-elected Mayor Lois Griffin.
We now go to Asian reporter
Tricia Takanawa
for her slant on the story.
Thanks, Tom.
Once again, happy locals are frolicking
in the waters of Lake Quahog,
and we're here with their reactions.
Sir, how does it feel to have the lake back?
Well, I'll tell you, Tricia, as a local resident,
I feel like I can once again take pride
in my community.
I think this is really gonna
revitalize tourism, and...
And, if you look around, I think
even the wildlife is starting to come back.
And, you know, that's something
we haven't seen in a while
and I think we're gonna be seeing
a lot more of that.
Hey, you guys.
Mom, everyone on TV says
you're running the town great.
Maybe you could do some damn laundry
once in a while.
- What?
- Wow, Mom, is that a new purse?
- Yeah, that looks pretty expensive.
Well, don't tell anybody, Brian,
but I was a little naughty.
(CHUCKLING)
I may have dipped into the tax surplus.
Wait a minute. You used taxpayer money
to buy yourself a handbag?
It's no big deal, Brian.
Besides, there was a lot left over
after the lake clean-up,
and I figured
maybe I earned a little treat, huh?
Lois, spending even one penny
of that money on yourself
- is incredibly unethical.
- Oh, come on, it was only 600.
My God, that's more than I spent
to go see that prize fight in Vegas.
I thought you said we was going
to see Hairspray.
Bitch, I thought I said just shut up
and be looking fine.
What the hell's up
with these rolling blackouts?
Well, since Lois is the mayor,
I'm allowed to reroute
all the town's electricity.
- What'd you do that for?
- So I could reanimate the corpse
- of Jim Varney.
- Howdy, Vern.
This is some dad-gum nice house
you got here, Vern.
That's Vern-Vern-Vern-Vern.
Oh, wait, wait. It was John Belushi.
That's who I wanted.
- Peter, how could you...
- Way ahead of you, Brian.
My mistake. I'll take care of this.
- Hey, Jim, come out in the yard, will you?
- Sure thing, Vern.
(GUN FIRING)
He got the shotgun, Brian!
Don't ask me how he did it,
but Jim Varney got the shotgun!
- Run for your life!
- What?
Run!
- Excuse me, how much is this coat?
- It's 4,300.
Oh. Do you think you can give me
a little mayoral discount?
Well, I think you're doing a great job,
Mrs. Griffin, but my boss would kill me.
- How's everything going out here?
- Fine, Mr. Voorhees.
Good. 'Cause if you screw up, I'll kill you.
Hi, Bob Grossbeard, Quahog Oil.
- I'd like to buy you that coat.
- Really?
All I ask in return
is that you let my company do
just a little bit of dumping in your lake.
This guy don't sit right with me, Lois.
He don't sit right with me.
- But I just cleaned up Quahog lake.
- Do you want the coat or not?
- I want the coat.
- Excellent. Then we have a deal.
(SIGHS)
Brian's gonna be really upset
when he finds out.
I'll just take him for a ride in the car,
he'll forget all about it.
(SNIFFING)
Wait a minute, I know where we are.
The park is near here!
We're near the park, Lois!
That's the tree, I peed on that!
Hey, hey, Lois! Lois!
There's another dog in that car!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Are you seeing that?
Hey! Hey! Hey, other dog! Fuck you!
Ladies and gentlemen,
on behalf of the Quahog Oil Refinery,
we would like to thank Mayor Lois Griffin
for our newest waste pipe.
(ALL CHEERING)
Let the dumping resume!
- What's going on?
- Everybody dead.
Oh, see now.
You know who they gonna blame this on.
Mmm-hmm. The black dolphins.
See, the honky dolphin always trying
to keep the black dolphin down.
I mean, can't we all just swim along?
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna call Fishy Jackson.
And you know what?
I'm gonna call Catfish Sharpton.
Get them motherfuckers on the line.
Hey, Jake,
how long can you hold
your breath underwater?
Longer than you! Check it out!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
My face!
(SCREAMING)
- Lois, what the hell are you doing?
- Remembering who I am, you crook!
Oh, I'm a crook, am I?
What about all the money you embezzled?
Do you want people to find out
about that?
You better play ball
or we'll find someone else who will.
I'll play ball.
You know what, West?
You can have your job back.
Politics does terrible things
to good people.
Good for you, Lois.
You wised up before it was too late.
I was so consumed by power and money,
I became the very thing
I set out to destroy.
Hooray, I'm mayor again!
Don't we need to have
a whole new election?
There. Now no one
will have heard him say that.
We all heard him say it.
- Anybody else hear anything?
- My wife did.
(GUN FIRING)
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru